Questions? Call [(206) 590-3278](tel:2065903278)

* Find a Facility

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy[ArenaSports Manager](https://www.arenasports.net/author/manager/ "Posts by ArenaSports Manager")2024-03-04T15:59:36-08:00

### **Refund Policy**

_Last updated on May 2023_

**Classes and Camps**

Arena Sports will gladly refund customers for any remaining classes and camps that they have not taken within the session, provided the events have _not_ passed on the calendar before the request has been sent. Any Camp refund requests must be received a week in advance of the registered day. All refund requests must be made in the form of an email to the facility or program personnel. In the event that a customer is unable to attend a class, they are required to inform Arena Sports. We will invite them to take a makeup class on another day, date, or time based on availability. Please note that makeup classes are not guaranteed. All makeup classes must be done during the season the missed class was scheduled in. Also, we will not grant any refunds “after the fact” of a no-show.

**Leagues and Teams**

After the customer pays their league fee, they are committed to the team/league and no refund will be granted except in the case of individual free agent players where a team is not found for the player by Arena Sports management.  The no refund policy includes games missed for any reason, including suspensions due to poor conduct within our facility and forfeited teams. Refunds are permitted only if the player finds a replacement that is acceptable to their teammates and team manager. The new player is required to make payment before any refund will be processed for the player leaving. Arena Sports will assist in the exchange while communicating with the players.

**All Other Transactions**

All other purchases, including but not limited to, pro-shop items, concession, food and drink, passes, family entertainment center attractions, and promotional sales are final and non-refundable.

### **TAXES AND FEES POLICY**

Some Arena Sports programs and products are subject to tax and fees. Taxes and fees are applied at check-out and itemized on receipts. Service Fees are 100% retained by Arena Sports and then distributed to our employees to provide competitive wages and benefits, allowing for exceptional customer service and experience.

### **PRIVACY NOTICE**

This Privacy Notice explains what information Arena Sports LLC (“**Arena Sports**” “**we**”, “**our**”, or “**us**”) collects about you when you visit this website [https://www.arenasports.net/](https://www.arenasports.net/) (the “**Website**”), how we use this information, with whom we share it, and the choices you have in connection with this.

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY**

Through your use of our Website, we collect personal information, which is information that identifies you as an individual, relates to you as an identifiable individual or, that along with other information, could identify you (collectively, “**Personal Information**”). We collect the following types of Personal Information:

**A. Information You Provide To Us.**

When you engage with certain aspects of our Website we collect Personal Information from you. This includes when you:

**Contact us by phone or email**. When you contact us or send us any feedback, comments, or suggestions, we collect from you any Personal Information you choose to include in such communication, as well as your phone number if you contact us by phone or your email address if you contact us by email.  We use this information to respond to your questions, feedback, comments, suggestions, or inquiries.

**Contact Us through Arena Sports Chat**. When you contact us or send us any feedback, comments, or suggestions on Arena Sports Chat, you will need to provide your name, email address, phone number, and a message, which could itself contain Personal Information.  Alternatively, you can contact us through Arena Sports Chat by signing in with Facebook or Google.  If you sign in with Facebook, you will need to provide the email address or phone number and password associated with your Facebook account.  If you sign in with Google, you will need to provide the email address or phone number associated with your Google account.  To log in with Facebook or Google, we use a service provider called Zendesk Chat.  You can review Zendesk Chat’s privacy policy [here](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/).  If you sign in with Google, Google will share your name, email address, language preference, and profile picture with Zendesk Chat.

**Apply for Employment****.** To apply for employment with us, we collect from you: your first and last name, address, phone number, email address, how you heard about us, the position for which you are applying, your availability, any information as may appear on your resume (if you choose to upload it), whether you have previously worked for Arena Sports, and any other Personal Information you choose to include in response to application questions. We also collect from you the first and last name, phone number, and email address of three references you provide. If you provide us with personal information of a reference or any other individual as part of your application, it is your responsibility to obtain consent from that individual prior to providing the information to us.

You have the option to provide us with information about your professional experience, and permit us to contact current and former employers. This includes the company name, address, phone number, start and end date, position, and reason for leaving. This also includes any training certificates, professional licenses and similar information. We may collect from you your education information, such as your high school and/or college name, start and end date, degree or level completed, and relevant coursework.

We use this information to respond to your application for employment.

**Create an Account.**  To create a member account, you will need to provide your first and last name, email address, gender, birthdate, address, phone number, emergency phone number, password and mobile phone number.  To create an account with us, we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation.  You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).  Creating an account with us will allow you to register for classes, tournaments, or camps, make a payment online, edit your profile, subscribe to your Calendar, add your Calendar to Google, subscribe to your location’s Calendar and add it to Google, add memberships, add passes, contact a location by including your email address, name, subject, phone number, and question/comment, and to view your statistics.

**Add Your Child to Your Account**.  If you add a child to your account, you will need to provide your child’s first and last name, date of birth, gender, and address.  You have the option to provide your child’s email, alternate email, phone numbers including day, night, mobile, emergency, and his or her mobile carrier.  You also have the option to set your child’s contact setting by selecting (1) send me email reminders about scheduled events (2) please don’t send any email to me (3) send me SMS event reminders and essential notices (4) show my phone and email information to others on my roster and (5) show my address information to others on my roster.  To add your child to your account with us, we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation. You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).

**Make an Advertising & Partnership Request.**  If you make an Advertising & Partnership Request to us, you will need to provide your name, email address, phone number, and comments/questions, which could itself contain Personal Information.  

**Interact with our Social Media.**  If you interact with us on our Facebook, Instagram, or LinkedIn account, we may collect your name, email address, photo, list of social media contacts, and any other information you make or which is accessible to us when you connect with us.  We collect this information to allow you to follow us, see our events, and interact with us.

**Schedule a Birthday Party Consultation or Birthday Party**.  If you schedule a birthday party consultation, you will need to provide your first and last name, phone number, email, child’s birth date, child’s first and last name, address, requested party date, types of activities, number of expected guests, and whether you are planning on ordering food.  If you book a birthday party, you will need to provide a date and time for the party, the party package type, an estimated amount of guests, and payment information (see below Make a Payment for the type of information).

**Make a Group & Corporate Event Request or Book a Group & Corporate Event**.  If you make an event request, you will need to provide your first and last name, group or company name, email address, phone number, preferred date, desired length of time, desired activities, and how you heard about us.  In addition, you have the option to provide an alternative date and comments in our comment box. If you book a group or corporate event, you will need to provide a date and time for the event, the play & food package type, an estimated amount of guests, and payment information (see below Make a Payment for the type of information).

**Get Notified About Registration for Camps**.  If you request to be notified about summer camp registration, you will need to provide your first and last name, email address, and check the box(es) for the program(s) you wish to be notified about.  In addition, you have the option to provide your preferred location.

**Get Notified About Registration for Classes or Leagues**.  If you request to be notified about class registration, you will need to provide your name, email address, which Arena Sports location you are interested in playing at, whether you are a new or returning player, and which season(s) you are interested in.  In addition, you have the option to provide your telephone number.

**Complete a Form “Players Looking for a Team”**.  If you fill out the form “Players Looking For A Team” you will need to provide your first and last name, email address, phone number, age, type of league, competition preference, and location.

**Complete a Form “Teams Looking for a Player”**.  If you fill out the form “Team Looking for a Player” you will need to provide your team name, team location, manager’s first and last name, phone number or email, and number of male and female players.

**Book a Free Trial Class for your Child**.  In order to register your child for a free trial class, you will need to provide your first and last name and your child’s first and last name, email address, phone number, what you are scheduling, and your child’s birth date.  In addition, you have the option of providing your address.

**Schedule a Make-Up Class**.  If you schedule a make-up class, you will need to select the date and time, and provide your child’s first and last name, your telephone number, your email address, and booking information (what you are scheduling, your child’s birthdate, parent’s first and last name).  In addition, you have the option of providing your address.

**Schedule or Register for Camps, Classes, Teams, Party & Events, Teams & Leagues, Tournaments & Cups, and other Programs.**  If you schedule or register on our Website for a camp, class, team, party, event, team, league, tournament, cup, or other program, you will need to login to your account.  See above for the Personal Information you must provide to create an account with us.   To schedule or register the above on our Website we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation.  You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).  If you register for a semi-private or private swimming class, you will need to fill out a form on our Website and provide your first and last name, phone number, child’s name, age, preferred time and a comment (optional).

**Make a payment**.  If you make a payment on our Website you will need to login to your account.  See above for the Personal Information you must provide to create an account with us.  To make a payment, you need to provide personal identifiers including your email address, first and last name, billing address, phone number, and your credit/debit card number, name on card, expiration date, security code.  To make a payment, we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation.  You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).

**Request a Donation**.  If you request a donation from Arena Sports, you will need to provide your name, email address, phone number, event information (including name, date, location, and description), charity information (organization, address, 501(c)(3) Tax ID #, and phone number).

**Use Our Message Center**.  In order to receive and send messages through our message center, you will need to create an account with us.  See above for the Personal Information you must provide to create an account.  When you use our message center, the text of the messages you send or receive may contain Personal Information. To provide our message center, we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation.  You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).

**Connect on our Website through Facebook**.  In order to login to our Website through Facebook, you will need to provide the email address or phone number and password associated with your Facebook account (your password will be hashed or encrypted).  After clicking on the “Connect using Facebook” button, you will be taken to Facebook.com where a notice states that we will receive your name, profile picture, birthday, and email address.  (You can click on the “edit this” link and change the setting for birthday if you do not wish for us to receive it; however, the rest of the information is required.)

**Use our Program Finder**.  In order to use our Program Finder, you will need to provide your date of birth or login to your account.  Our Program Finder allows you to reveal a customized list of classes, leagues, and camps that match your preferences.

**Attend an Open House**.  In order to attend at open house, you will need to provide your child’s first and last name, your child’s birth date, your first and last name, email address and phone number.

**Dine at Moe’s Kitchen**. In order to dine at Moe’s Kitchen, you will need to provide your credit card information (account number and security code) through our service provider called DaySmart Recreation. You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/). If you have an existing DaySmart Recreation profile, in addition to the collection of your credit card information, we may collect your purchase history for future promotions.

**Promotional emails or text messages**.  If you sign up for promotional emails and/or text messages, we collect from you your name, email address, and phone number. If you sign up for one of our programs, we may also enroll you in promotional emails automatically and to this end will collect the same information. You may opt out of receiving these email communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email. You may opt out of receiving these text messages from us by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.arenasports.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and requesting to no longer receive these messages.

**B. Information Collected Automatically**

When you use our Websites, we use cookies and other technologies to automatically collect certain information about you. Cookies are text files that your web browser places on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies stay on your device for a set period of time or until you delete them, while session cookies expire when you close your web browser. The cookies and other technologies deployed on our Websites collect the following information:

**Usage Information**. Such as the pages on our Websites you access, the frequency of access, what you click on, and when you access the Websites.

**Location Information**. Information about your location, which may be determined through your IP address or geolocation.

**Device Information**. Information about the device you are using, such as hardware model, operating system, browser, and your Website preferences.

In particular, we utilize the following cookies:

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**. These cookies are required for making use of our Websites. These cookies include security cookies to authenticate users, prevent fraudulent use of our Websites, and protect user data from unauthorized parties. Our strictly necessary cookies allow our Websites to function and allow you to use the features of our Websites.

**Analytics Cookies**. We use Google Analytics to collect information on your use of the Website to improve our Website. In order to collect this information, Google Analytics may set cookies on your browser, or read cookies that are already there. Google Analytics may also receive information about you from applications you have downloaded that partner with Google. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our Website or to another application which partners with Google is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Please review those policies [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Advertising Cookies****.**  We utilize [Google](http://www.google.com/) Doubleclick by to serve ads that appear on Google products and on sites across the Internet. Google places cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies to serve you ads based on past visits to our Websites. Each customer receives a different conversion cookie. The information collected by the cookie is used to generate conversion statistics and allows us to see the total number of individuals who clicked on our ads. Please review Google’s privacy policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) for additional information on how Google uses the information collected. You can control how Google uses your information through Google’s [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/).

We also use Google Remarketing to display advertisements to you about our goods and services across the internet, including on other websites you visit based on the fact that you have visited our website. Google may also display other advertisements across the internet to you about third party services using the Google AdSense network, although this is beyond our control. For more information about Google remarketing, click [here](https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/2453998?hl=en).

The [Pinterest](https://www.pinterest.com/) Conversion Tag collects site behavior data to show content that’s relevant, interesting and personal to users when visiting the Pinterest website or browsing the Pinterest app. Our website uses the Pinterest Conversion Tag to recognize when a user visits our website, perform conversion tracking, target advertisements which may be of particular interest to specific users and validate authenticated user sessions. Through Pinterest tags, Pinterest is informed of what website pages and products you have viewed on our site. This information enables us to display personalized ads on Pinterest’s website and apps.  If you land on one of our ads via a pin, this information will be processed by Pinterest and communicated to us as statistics (conversions). This allows us to find out, for instance, how many users have clicked on our pins. We obtain no information that allows users to be personally identified.  You can opt out of online behavioral advertising through Pinterest’s personalization settings [here](https://help.pinterest.com/en/article/personalization-and-data) or through the Digital Advertising Alliance [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). You can learn more about Pinterest’s Privacy Policy including their services and your rights [here](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).

We use [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/) Pixel to customize our advertising and to serve you ads on your social media based on your browsing behavior. This allows your behavior to be tracked after you have been redirected to our website by clicking on the Facebook ad. The Facebook Pixel stores a cookie on your computer to enable us to measure the effectiveness of Facebook ads for statistical and market research purposes. We do not have access to the personal information collected through the Facebook Pixel. However, the information collected via the Facebook Pixel, on our website as well as other websites on which Facebook Pixel is installed, is also stored and processed by Facebook. Facebook may link this information to your Facebook account and also use it for its own promotional purposes in accordance with Facebook’s [Data Usage Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/). The Facebook Pixel also allows Facebook and its partners to show you advertisements on and outside of Facebook. You can opt-out of displaying Facebook ads by visiting your Facebook [Ad Settings](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads), and you can clear and control the information third parties share with Facebook in your [Off-Facebook Activity](https://www.facebook.com/off_facebook_activity/) page. If you do not have a Facebook account, you can opt-out of Facebook ads through the Digital Advertising Alliance [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

**2\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use the Personal Information we collect about you to:

* Process your payments.
* Respond to your questions, feedback, comments, suggestions, or inquiries.
* Respond to your application for employment.
* Provide you or your child with a user account.
* Respond to your advertising and partnership request.
* Interact with you on social media.
* Permit you to purchase food at Moe’s Kitchen and to provide future Moe’s Kitchen promotions.
* Permit you to schedule a birthday party consultation with us.
* Respond to your group or corporate event request.
* Notify you about registration for classes, leagues, and camps, in addition to game reminders and promotional messages.
* Help you find a team or a player.
* Provide your child with a free trial class.
* Permit you to schedule a make-up class.
* Permit you to schedule or register for camps, classes, party & events, teams & leagues, tournaments & cups, and other programs.
* Respond to your request for a donation.
* Communicate with you about our Website or to inform you of any changes to our Website.
* Send you information on new products and/or services we feel may be of interest to you.
* Engage in internet-based advertising.
* Maintain and improve our Website and the services offered thereon.
* Diagnose Website problems and engage in fraud identification and prevention.
* Monitor user experience.
* Defend our rights and those of others.
* Efficiently maintain our business.
* Comply with the law.

We also process and share information in an aggregated, de-identified manner, where the information is shared as part of a statistical report and does not contain personal information.

**3\. HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We share your Personal Information for the purposes set forth below.

**Service Providers**. We share Personal Information with our service providers, such as payment processors, email providers, advertising providers, and analytics providers. We limit the information shared with our service providers to what is necessary to fulfill the services. We use the following providers:

**Payment Processor.** To make a payment, we use a service provider called DaySmart Recreation.  You can review DaySmart Recreation’s privacy policy [here](https://www.daysmartrecreation.com/privacy-policy/).

**Analytics** **Providers**.  We use Google Analytics to collect information on your use of the Website to improve our Website. You may view Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Scheduling**.  We use Acuity Scheduling to facilitate online scheduling.  Acuity Scheduling is part of Squarespace and its privacy policy can be viewed [here](https://www.squarespace.com/privacy).

**Other Third Parties**.  We utilize Google Doubleclick to serve ads that appear on Google products and on sites across the Internet.  To opt out of targeted advertising by Google, you can go to Google’s [ad settings](https://adssettings.google.com/).  You may also install the [DoubleClick opt-out add-on](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/plugin?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCigvVYAN17ugYRMwQf_InKv4i5GKLPNen5UUD8qFqiWU4vtXR5jsz_uaOHdJqvhufEjezDh-Q13icRRRab9WJDGpQbwkQ). Once installed, even if you clear all your cookies and restart your browser, it will prevent the DoubleClick cookie from being saved to your browser. We also utilize Google Remarketing to display advertisements to you about our goods and services across the internet, including on other websites you visit based on the fact that you have visited our website. Google may also display other advertisements across the internet to you about third party services using the Google AdSense network, although this is beyond our control. For more information about Google remarketing, click [here](https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/2453998?hl=en). We also use Google Maps provide the Virtual Tour functionality on our website. Google collects Personal Information from you through the Google Map cookies used to provide the Virtual Tour. Please review Google’s [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en) for additional information on how Google uses the information collected for Google Doubleclick and Google Maps.

**Within Arena Sports**. We share Personal Information within our corporate family, such as with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or affiliates, in order to efficiently carry out our business and to the extent permitted by law.

**Corporate Reorganization**. In the event that we enter into, or intend to enter into, a transaction that alters the structure of our business, such as a reorganization, merger, acquisition, sale, joint venture, assignment, consolidation, transfer, change of control, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock, we would share personal information with third parties, including the buyer or target (and their agents and advisors) for the purpose of facilitating and completing the transaction. We would also share Personal Information with third parties if we undergo bankruptcy or liquidation, in the course of such proceedings.

**To Prevent Harm**. We will share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary to detect, investigate, prevent, or take action against illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the rights, property, or personal safety of any person.

**Legal Purposes****.** We will share Personal Information where we are legally required to do so, such as in response to court orders, law enforcement or legal process, including for national security purposes; to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights, as required to enforce our terms of service or other contracts; to defend against legal claims or demands; or to comply with the requirements of any applicable law.

**With Your Consent**. We may request your permission to share your Personal Information for a specific purpose. We will notify you and request consent before you provide the Personal Information or before the Personal Information you have already provided is shared for such purpose.

**4\. CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION**

**Update Account Information**.  You can update your account information (including your address, phone number, email address, fitness interests, username, password, and payment methods) at any time by logging in to your user account.

**Online Advertising.** To opt-out of interest based advertising generally or to learn more about the use of this information you can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You can also visit the privacy settings of your Android or iOS device and select “limit ad tracking” (Apple iOS) or “opt-out of interest-based ads” (Android).

**Google Analytics****.** You can control the information provided to Google and opt-out of certain by using one of the methods set forth [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can also download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Promotional Emails**. You may opt-out of receiving marketing emails from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link provided with each email. Please note that we will continue to send you notifications necessary to the Website, the services, and your purchases.

**Promotional Text Messages**.  With your consent, we may send you promotional text messages. You can opt out of these text messages at any time by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.arenasports.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and requesting to no longer receive these messages.

**Cookies.** All session cookies expire after you close your browser. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser’s directions. To find out how to see what cookies have been set on your device, and how to reject and delete the cookies, please visit: [https://www.aboutcookies.org/](https://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that each browser is different. For information on reviewing or deleting cookies from specific browsers, click on the appropriate browser: [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/clear-cookies-and-site-data-firefox), [Firefox IOS](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/clear-browsing-history-firefox-ios), [Firefox Android](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/clear-your-browsing-history-and-other-personal-data), [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac), [Safari Mobile](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265), [Chrome](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en), [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies), [Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4027947/windows-delete-cookies), [Opera](https://help.opera.com/en/latest/security-and-privacy/#clearBrowsingData). To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer’s website. If you reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, some features of our Website may not function properly. If you choose to opt-out, we will place an “opt-out cookie” on your computer. The “opt-out cookie” is browser and device specific and only lasts until cookies are cleared from your browser or device. The opt-out cookie will not work for strictly necessary cookies. If the cookie is removed or deleted, if you upgrade your browser or if you visit us from a different computer, you will need to return and update your preferences.

**Location Settings**. You may prevent your device from sharing your location data by adjusting the permissions on your device.

**5\. DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE**

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your browser. For further details, visit [https://www.eff.org/issues/do-not-track](https://www.eff.org/issues/do-not-track).

**6\. INFORMATION SECURITY**

We implement and maintain commercially reasonable security measures to protect the Personal Information we collect. Our security measures include but are not limited to TLS 1.2 and Google reCAPTCHA.  However, no security measure or modality of data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you transferred over the Internet.

**7\. THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Our Website may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. This Privacy Notice applies solely to the Personal Information collected on our Website. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party’s website. We strongly advise you to review the privacy notice of every website you visit.

**8\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**

Arena Sports LLC reserves the right to amend this Privacy Notice at our discretion and at any time. Changes to the Privacy Notice will be posted on this page and will indicate the date the changes go into effect. Please check back and review the Privacy Notice for any changes. If we make any changes that materially affect your privacy rights, we will announce those changes by posting the revised Privacy Notice on our Website and will always indicate the date the last changes were published.  If changes are significant, we will provide notice in an additional means we deem appropriate which may include directly notifying you by email.

**9\. CONTACT**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, please contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.arenasports.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**This Privacy Notice was last modified on March 4, 2024**

### ABOUT US

Arena Sports is a family-run business focused on family fun. We offer year-round soccer for people of all ages and abilities. Plus we have super cool indoor inflatable FunZones, awesome camps, and rockin' birthday parties. [Learn more about Arena Sports](https://www.arenasports.net/about-us/).

Copyright 2024 Arena Sports | [Refund & Privacy Policy](https://www.arenasports.net/privacy-policy/)

### GET EMAIL UPDATES

This form needs Javascript to display, which your browser doesn't support. [Sign up here](https://app.e2ma.net/app2/audience/signup/1971321/1788021/) instead

#### Stay Connected!

#### Arena Sports Network

#### Looking for these?

")
